I've got to order the Regars, the Regars scheduled City Council be for Tuesday, October 21, 2020, bye.
Doug Kimfield, let's get to personal chances. We have none.
Item 3, A, claims list.
Who's two proof?
Is it a double?
Aye.
Item B, minutes from the October 7, 2021, regular B.
Motion approved?
Second.
Aye.
Resolution.
CC 2025-13.
Cupification of the Monacoat of Wardensis.
To include supplement 21.
This is just required.
This is the order of one thing.
No.
Second.
Shows.
Aye.
Do you remember?
To wardens to allow council members to carry barons and see council maves adding chapter, article, and section?
This is just an amendment to what you passed last week.
I forgot to put the chapter, article, and section, and that seems to get me a lot.
I guess some cities don't do that, right?
I suppose.
Maybe if I don't do what we just did in an item C.
Motion approved.
Second.
Aye.
NO.
The nomination, too.
The livations.
Aye.
No.
Not.
We need to have somebody there in the interim until the battle of the updated.
I think we can update the Bileau next week.
So what I think the board, their board, the 501C3 board has to amend them.
So at the annual meeting, they would have to vote to change the Bileau's at that meeting
and then they can vote on the candidates and it's by secret ballot.
So if, for some reason, the 501C3 says they don't want to update the Bileau's, then we...
have to have a backup person from the council.
I mean, I don't know why they wouldn't, but just.
If I need to do it, I can't.
Okay.
Thank you.
We'll be there.
We're so in the way we have to appoint the board members.
So, Kelly, kind of put together a list of some people that are interested in serving on the board.
I think there's some big shoes to fill.
Yes, I did put a list of people that were interested on their two halves that are currently serving
and said they would continue on to our active members that come out every week and are involved
and then the other one is a city representative.
So, do they not have to go to the online portal that we have posted?
It's a 501C3, not a city advisory board, gotcha.
Good question.
Yeah, it was a good question.
Which we had about a lot of interest in people that's the meeting for boards on how to deal with these.
Is that what's in our website in case I was like, I want to serve them.
We've been directing people there.
Sweet.
We want more.
Okay.
No, if we need to go ahead and make the approval for this, we have to have it published
and in the paper, no less than one week before the meeting, which is the second Wednesday
of the month.
So, they have to approve the by-law changes, but we can approve this list of either heaven or
brian, depending on if they approve that change or not.
It's your time to you guys.
We have a work session scheduled for next week so we can do it next week too.
If you guys want to think about more members.
Which is fine.
Yeah.
I'll have a problem with you later.
Do we approve it pending there approval?
Or...
I don't know.
So, it's in the by-laws.
Hold on.
I had it.
This was a confusing for me.
And this also is just the 501C3.
I'm not sure if we're going to dismiss the advisory board because it's the same set of
people, but this was just for the 501C3 board.
And so it does say the City Council shall nominate the directors of the organization, at least
one of which shall be from the Council's own members regardless of age and remainder will be
members of the organization.
And then it says that they have to vote it in at their annual meeting by seat.
I have a question because I'm confused as well.
So 501, C3 board.
Same people as a city advisory board.
Yeah.
Okay.
Why are we approving for the 501, C3,
if we're a city,
the way that the file of the written,
we nominate the direction of the board.
So we took over.
But they're all the same people.
Technically the advisory board never meets,
because it is the same people.
So it's canceled.
The advisory board meetings have been canceled every month.
And then the 501 C3 board meetings have been canceled.
Yeah.
A bigger problem in my opinion,
that you have.
Another 501 C3 that the city has been the city funds to maintain.
We have more putting manpower.
And but it's also an asset that the city owns.
But we should be nominating to the advisory board.
But the advisory board.
I mean the advisory board and the 501 C3 board are the same.
Yeah.
I would say we have to keep the advisory board just.
This is because the way it's created.
I think that we've been nominating for approve this list.
And then if that meeting have the bylaws.
Requested the bylaws we change.
So.
Change.
What?
You say city manager.
City manager or his.
He or his or her doesn't mean.
Yeah.
Isn't that how we wrote it coming.
We haven't finished anything.
It's all still.
That would be.
That would make it the easiest.
Just.
Then.
Yeah.
I mean.
So Kevin.
Yeah.
Just a point.
Someone else that spot.
Yeah.
Or if he's not the.
So you're managing more than new.
You might want to be there.
Yeah.
They could have twice the month of that spot.
I still thank you.
It could be a lot of this.
So the.
So the
five questions to people.
So we're in about a month and a year.
So that.
So the girl.
How are you.
So the.
So.
So, patterns are over here, but I can speak to that legally speaking.
They're already not for the friends of the library the friends of the library has a statement that says that they raised funds to give to the library and for operations and things
But the auditor just said there's a lot of cities do it like this. It's just not the best
Just tell me a lot of
Do we create a friend of the senior center? I think you just get them to vote to change it to that and then they have to have somebody else managing their own funds and a statement that says that they
They are their purposes to help raise money to keep the operations at the senior center going and then that way they could we could request like we do at the library
We say hey you guys have a meeting coming up. We have this program. We need funds for they write a check and they
Help pay for it. I mean that would be with this idea
Yeah, so you know the five one see three just gets the money from the what is it you know I didn't wait
They're certain grants we have to have a five one
I think it's a process
I mean
They are not, they're not at this.
You come out of the senior center, so.
Yes.
Well, I think that's kind of what got the senior center in a mess.
And why we?
It is exactly what got it in there.
And at this point, those problems had gone to the end.
We were taking it back and we're trying to get it on it.
So, but if you're talking about totally separated,
it's something that would be different.
But I like to think we saw that whenever we took building an over.
And over on for the one that we're trying to.
Well, and as I stated before, the majority of the funds are city funds,
not 501c3 funds, so that United Way funding isn't going to keep the senior center open anyway.
It's.
So, so all you think they would be over is the the United Way funds.
Or any other raising funds, anything that they get from they can apply for granted insurance.
Membership.
But that's still in account.
You know what I mean?
And the girls.
Then if I have to do an excellent job of separating the two different funds.
So, they know, like, and counting, getting the great job separated.
So, there's visibility.
There's been zero lack of transparency on any of this.
It's very clear about that.
So, it's not like anybody's hiding anything.
I think.
If money.
If money was.
No object.
They would have their own.
It's going to happen.
I mean, it's going to take.
Years to get it up and move.
To build a sustain that kind of model.
If we still.
If we still want to bring in money on the capital.
One, see three, so.
Two donations and anything.
The.
They're.
Who.
The.
Here.
Third.
The.
This.
And cool.
tax exempt entity. And we are designated that way because the IRS code intends for non-profits
to do their thing, governmental entities to do their thing. So technically the spirit of the law
does not intend for the two to merge. So if that united way is to donate to a municipality or
governmental entity, they need to change their by laws to allow that. Because currently it doesn't
sound like it's intended to go to a municipality of those funds. So I guess I'll ask you this question,
is the $4,000, $250 worth? We have had a sustainability without it. We would just have to.
So far Reynolds have been doing very well. So Kevin, Kevin, do you have any good ideas for fundraisers?
So, yeah, I did. So, in the manner. Could we not just accept this?
It seems like $4,000 in one by the setting. Yeah. Y'all guys are speaking up about this stuff.
Well, I'm just saying if we're going to go into that, I mean, going back to the advisory board,
that hasn't met because we have a policy for you. And I don't even think we have an ordinance for
enough advisory board, do we? This council wrote an advisory board. The council is going to run
the matters of the senior center. That was the intent when it was acquired, right? Cali and Cindy
know the senior center inside and out. They, I mean, I think they can provide adequate information for
the council to make informed decisions regarding the senior center. So I don't know. For me, if I need to
come do once a month report like I do currently for you guys, I mean, I can do that, provide the number of
people that came in, all the meals we stole, etc. I can put it in the packet every meeting or once a month.
No member. I tell no member.
I'll be there.
Yeah, I'll be there.
What kind of thing I have to do?
No, we just have the one through the 501C3.
That's the United Way.
All the other grants are just sitting.
No, no, no.
It's the only one.
And it's 4,000 turn per dollar.
Why are you?
It's eight.
Okay.
85,000 per dollar.
And that's if they're fundraisers,
bring in enough money.
It's not always guaranteed.
So it could be less.
So eight by five.
Yeah.
And things like that.
A lot of money.
What kind of money?
For our whole staff.
And we did shoot out by the office.
I know it's money that he's not.
He's not.
I don't know.
Our taxpayer funds right now.
But that made it.
It is.
From another pot.
Well, I think it's.
Awareness that he needs to grow about it.
The rentals have.
Absolutely.
The rental fee.
I think it's going to be able to calculate.
On the rental.
The usage fee.
And it's having the facility open.
I mean, I have a rental booked for October of next year.
Right.
Already.
But it sounds like it got the problems for accounting staff.
It's problems for.
Legals that.
Just a computer.
It's always.
Trying to keep it.
So.
Yeah.
It's $10,055.
It's budgeted for the final one.
See three on the senior center.
But if the final one.
See three continues.
There's nothing stopping it from continuing to.
It just means to be separated.
Correct.
We have a 501 3C at the airport.
It's fun.
I'm just asking.
I mean.
It's not a stipulation of those types of grants.
It would be an on top of it.
Okay.
Got you.
So it's a stipulation.
The United Way.
Yes.
Yeah.
But I want to.
We.
It's important.
If you remember we took it over because the United Way was giving money at the time and
to continue to give money.
Right.
And at the time.
Everything was.
This needs to be able to fund itself.
We need the only money.
Find all the money we can.
Yeah.
We can't take it off.
So.
So we went and found money.
Yeah.
And we went and found a tear.
We've done all the things.
There's a lot of goes into accepting.
$800 from the United Way.
So.
For.
To make that made for.
We just need to vote for the people right.
And then we can worry about everything else.
We go right.
So this is something.
You guys are going to.
I'm separate.
Or.
You guys may do.
Microsoft and other.
That's a big.
Thank you.
Get the time.
It's.
If.
So.
Good.
If.
Go.
I have a question before we finish.
You said through the flag.
I did say through the flag.
We're voting on a list of names that might be moved to favor against having one of these people and not a council person on their board.
So we can do that.
I don't approve it.
Continue on there.
There we go.
I feel better about that.
I forgot to add that for it.
Thank you.
I did.
Thank you everybody.
Five staff reports.
The VA report on city manager budget member's team.
Foundation credit balance.
As of 9 to 30 20 25.
C facilities.
Approved.
The.
That.
That's one of the member.
I could give.
Oh,
Nice.
You.
For that.
157.
I jou Got.
You.
That's all.
Yeah.
So, you had to think this is like they have about that.
That's four.
and I'll take credit.
And that was to help us pay that lump sum.
Get them.
Yep.
Okay.
Any other questions, though?
Those six barren council community announcements.
Go and say the chat.
Get point out there.
I'd like to recognize Eric Barnes coming.
He's in my class of leadership 28.
So.
I'll start with Eric Barnes.
So as a founder of British University,
I'm going to ask you that it is a requirement of class community.
There's.
We need to be here.
So.
I really just need a sign to help you be a gender.
Not being joined myself.
I mean, I'll go to a city council meeting before.
Thanks, Eric.
Thank you.
So your friends were here.
The bull buck out.
The bull bash went.
We're very well.
I'll make sure.
No issues whatsoever.
We're going to have to decide.
He didn't almost die. Look like he did you see he walked away out of the hospital
So he didn't almost died. He didn't walk out of the Buffalo ring the bull bash went well and everything good
We had a good. It was perfect. He was awesome
I missed the bull bash because I was on vacation with my life
We're implored it and I got to visit with three mayors while I was in Florida
Three communities of the island we're on
It was quite interesting. I thought to meet her
10 or 15 men's feet but it's funny that even in paradise
They have the same issues. We have here
You know they talk about the people who complain about the roads about jobs
And they all brought up nice sayers
So
Seems like no matter where you go and do you meet and it's on a council or somewhere
We have the same issues and every community around so
But it was good that work for those guys and I've been riding them all in
66 nice years off my bottle
It was it was a good trip. It was a good trip. I'm not ashamed of my whole song. I've been in the University of Canada
I'm giving her a concealed carry life
Anybody else
I'm just like
I said run everybody the sipping shop and then also let everybody know they're trying to has been asked to be on the Route 60 6 board
She just got busy
That's all I have
What is the least he's open to my house?
It's better
Let's get out of here. We still got clothes
All right
Is that it?
Yes, it's eight in a minute
Well, second
I still
I
Parker
I'll sign your paper
Now we
He's already did it
Oh, you did it. He's gone
He's gone